<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Job Positions on Nubificus Ltd</title>
    <link>/jobs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Job Positions on Nubificus Ltd</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 11 Jul 2021 11:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/jobs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>EU Project Manager (EPMR)</title>
      <link>/jobs/job6/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jul 2021 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/jobs/job6/</guid>
      <description>Responsibilities:
 Plan and organize project activities, perform risk management and propose contingency measures and adaptations to achieve project goals Directly implement projects’ activities such as organizing field research, drafting studies/reports/deliverables, planning &amp;amp; organizing events, etc., according to the project needs, as well as financial and human resources limitations Coordinate the implementation of projects’ tasks when assigned to project partners and/or colleagues ensuring final delivery Ensure comprehensive and up-to-date project documentation Contribute to new project ideas generation and development opportunities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DevOps Engineer (DER)</title>
      <link>/jobs/job7/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 May 2021 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/jobs/job7/</guid>
      <description>Responsibilities:
 Define and set development, test, release, update, and support processes for the product and service offerings. Implement and set up development, testing, automation tools, and IT infrastructure. Plan the team structure, activities, and participate in project management activities Monitor the processes during the entire lifecycle for its adherence and update or create new processes for improvement. Encourage and build automated processes wherever possible Evaluate / select / build and deploy appropriate CI/CD tools  Requirements:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Systems Software Engineer (SSSER)</title>
      <link>/jobs/job1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 May 2021 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/jobs/job1/</guid>
      <description>Responsibilities:
 Develop software and research for a cutting edge technology project Design and develop reusable and reliable code using at least one of the following: C / Python / GO / C++ / Rust Partake in all aspects of the project’s life cycle Research and solve complex engineering challenges Lead a small team of engineers and coordinate effort to achieve short-term goals Lead upstreaming efforts to contribute to open-source projects Communicate the team&amp;rsquo;s findings &amp;amp; results to company&amp;rsquo;s partners  Requirements:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Software Engineer (SER)</title>
      <link>/jobs/job3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 May 2021 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/jobs/job3/</guid>
      <description>Responsibilities:
 Develop software for a cutting edge technology project Design and develop reusable and reliable code using at least one of the following: C / Python / GO / C++ / Rust Participate in upstreaming efforts to contribute to open-source projects  Requirements:
 Minimum 3 years of experience in software development BSc or MSc degree in Computer Science/Engineering, Telecommunications or similar Good understanding of best practices in software development Working knowledge of control systems like git Working knowledge of Go Familiarity with container runtimes and orchestrators (Kubernetes) Proficiency in spoken and written English Ability to work in a distributed team  Location:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Systems Software Engineer (SSER)</title>
      <link>/jobs/job2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 May 2021 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/jobs/job2/</guid>
      <description>Responsibilities:
 Develop software for a cutting edge technology project Design and develop reusable and reliable code using at least one of the following: C / Python / GO / C++ / Rust Participate in upstreaming efforts to contribute to open-source projects  Requirements:
 Minimum 3 years of experience in software development BSc or MSc degree in Computer Science/Engineering, Telecommunications or similar Good understanding of best practices in software development Working knowledge of C Working knowledge of control systems like git Experience with Linux kernel and virtualization development Proficiency in spoken and written English Ability to work in a distributed team  Location:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Software Engineer / Intern (SEITFR)</title>
      <link>/jobs/job4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2019 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/jobs/job4/</guid>
      <description>Internship title: Explore TF internal operations to be offloaded to a generic transport mechanism
Short description:
Tensorflow supports offloading computations on hardware accelerators (GPUs, TPUs). In order to use an accelerator, a Tensorflow instance currently needs direct access to the relevant hardware. Although this requirement doesn&amp;rsquo;t prevent distributed deployments (either by Tensorflow itself or by higher level frameworks like pycharm) in heterogeneous hardware, it limits flexibility of integrating hardware accelerators to virtualized setups where Tensorflow applications are executed, especially when there are latency constraints (ie.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Application Engineer / Intern (AEIBR)</title>
      <link>/jobs/job5/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 May 2018 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/jobs/job5/</guid>
      <description>Internship title: BLAS bindings to the vAccel framework
Short description:
The BLAS (Basic Linear Algebra Subprograms) are routines that provide standard building blocks for performing basic vector and matrix operations. The Level 1 BLAS perform scalar, vector and vector-vector operations, the Level 2 BLAS perform matrix-vector operations, and the Level 3 BLAS perform matrix-matrix operations.
vAccel is a framework offering hardware acceleration primitives with focus on portability. It exposes &amp;ldquo;accelerate-able&amp;rdquo; functions to programmers and abstracts away hardware complexity by means of a pluggable design.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>